// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "According to the Aufbau principle, in which order are electrons filled in atomic orbitals?",
    answer: "1s, 2s, 2p, 3s, 3p, 4s, 3d, 4p",
    options: [
      "1s, 2s, 2p, 3s, 3p, 4s, 3d, 4p",
      "2s, 2p, 3s, 3p, 4s, 3d, 4p, 5s",
      "1s, 2s, 2p, 3s, 3p, 4s, 4d, 5s",
      "2s, 2p, 3s, 3p, 4s, 4d, 5s, 5p"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which principle states that a maximum of two electrons, each with opposite spins, can fit in an orbital?",
    answer: "Pauli exclusion principle",
    options: [
      "Pauli exclusion principle",
      "Hund's rule",
      "Aufbau principle",
      "Octet rule"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "According to Hund's rule, how are electrons filled in orbitals belonging to a subshell?",
    answer: "Every orbital is singly occupied by electrons before a second electron is filled in an orbital.",
    options: [
      "Every orbital is singly occupied by electrons before a second electron is filled in an orbital.",
      "Electrons fill orbitals in a random order within a subshell.",
      "Electrons fill orbitals in increasing order of their energies.",
      "Electrons fill orbitals in decreasing order of their energies."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the electron configuration of hydrogen?",
    answer: "1s1",
    options: [
      "1s1",
      "1s2 2s2 2p4",
      "1s2 2s2 2p4",
      "[Ne]3s23p5"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How many electrons are in the oxygen atom?",
    answer: "8",
    options: [
      "4",
      "6",
      "8",
      "17"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the electron configuration of oxygen?",
    answer: "1s2 2s2 2p4",
    options: [
      "1s2 2s2 2p4",
      "1s1",
      "1s2 2s2 2p6",
      "[Ne]3s23p5"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the electron configuration of chlorine?",
    answer: "1s22s22p63s23p5",
    options: [
      "1s2 2s2 2p4",
      "1s1",
      "1s22s22p63s23p5",
      "[Ne]3s23p5"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 8,
    question: "How many electrons are in the chlorine atom?",
    answer: "17",
    options: [
      "2",
      "6",
      "7",
      "17"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which principle states that electrons occupy orbitals with lower energy before occupying higher energy orbitals?",
    answer: "Aufbau principle",
    options: [
      "Aufbau principle",
      "Pauli exclusion principle",
      "Hund's rule",
      "Octet rule"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which atomic orbitals are filled after the 4s subshell according to the Aufbau principle?",
    answer: "3d",
    options: [
      "3d",
      "5s",
      "4p",
      "6s"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which is not true about amorphous solids?",
    answer: "Anisotrophic",
    options: [
      "IMF are not equal",
      "Irregular arrangement",
      "Anisotrophic",
      "Shapeless"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 12,
    question: "What is a force within a single molecule?",
    answer: "Intramolecular Forces",
    options: [
      "Net Force",
      "London Bridge Forces",
      "Intramolecular Forces",
      "Negative Force"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Strong Intermolecular forces but Low kinetic energy",
    answer: "Solid",
    options: [
      "Solid",
      "Water",
      "amorphous",
      "Gas"
    ]
  },
    { 
    numb: 14,
    question: "Two or more substance are mixed together to form a solution",
    answer: "Solution",
    options: [
      "Experiment",
      "Goku",
      "Solute",
      "Solution"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What is the substance that dissolves solute?",
    answer: "Solvent",
    options: [
      "Luffy",
      "Solvent",
      "Naruto",
      "bolpen"
    ]
  },
]